<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<RelativeLayout xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android"
    xmlns:app="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res-auto"
    xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools"
    android:layout_width="match_parent"
    android:layout_height="match_parent"
    android:gravity="center">
    <androidx.constraintlayout.widget.ConstraintLayout
        android:layout_width="match_parent"
        android:layout_height="match_parent">

        <androidx.appcompat.widget.Toolbar
            android:id="@+id/toolbar"
            android:layout_width="408dp"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:layout_alignParentStart="true"
            android:layout_alignParentEnd="true"
            android:layout_marginStart="209dp"
            android:layout_marginEnd="202dp"
            android:background="#B4357C25"
            app:layout_constraintEnd_toEndOf="parent"
            app:layout_constraintHorizontal_bias="0.509"
            app:layout_constraintStart_toStartOf="parent"
            app:layout_constraintTop_toTopOf="parent"
            app:title="Game Review" />



    </androidx.constraintlayout.widget.ConstraintLayout>
    <ImageView
        android:id="@+id/game_icon"
        android:layout_width="100dp"
        android:layout_height="100dp"
        android:adjustViewBounds="true"
        android:scaleType="centerCrop"
        android:src="@drawable/img_5"
        tools:layout_editor_absoluteX="11dp"
        tools:layout_editor_absoluteY="129dp"
        android:layout_marginTop="100dp"/>


    <LinearLayout
    android:layout_width="match_parent"
    android:layout_height="wrap_content"
    android:orientation="vertical"
    android:padding="16dp">

        <LinearLayout
        android:layout_width="0dp"
        android:layout_height="wrap_content"
        android:layout_weight="1"
        android:orientation="vertical"
        android:paddingLeft="16dp">

        <TextView
            android:id="@+id/game_title"
            android:layout_width="wrap_content"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:text="Game Title"
            android:textSize="20sp"
            android:textStyle="bold" />

        <TextView
            android:id="@+id/developer_name"
            android:layout_width="wrap_content"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:text="By: Developer Name" />

        <TextView
            android:id="@+id/genre_tags"
            android:layout_width="wrap_content"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:text="Genre: Action, Adventure" />

    </LinearLayout>

    <LinearLayout
        android:layout_width="match_parent"
        android:layout_height="wrap_content"
        android:orientation="vertical"
        android:padding="16dp">

        <RatingBar
            android:id="@+id/rating_bar"
            android:layout_width="wrap_content"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:numStars="5"
            android:stepSize="1.0" />

        <TextView
            android:id="@+id/review_text"
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:text="
[Spoiler free] This game could quite literally be the best game of out generation, not many games get such high praise but this game unequivocally deserves it. Is breath taking graphics and unbeatable gameplay are only a page in a massive book on things why this game is amazing. The story is a magnificent compelling attribute to an already perfect game, the story draws you in by constantly keeping you on a train of cliff hangers and systems where it make you want to unlock other plots advancing the story, all the while making each and every advancement into the plot as fresh as the previous one. The gritty nature of the story at heart is just a small layer shadowing the deeper lesson of understanding and acceptance of past actions. The game play is utterly brilliant, the fighting mechanics and the abilities are unseen is a franchise about hack and slash, while still retaining the incredibly addictive playability of not only it’s own series but of any game genre of us kind. The blocking in this game doesn’t just defend you from an enemy’s attacks is allowed you to counter damaging them stunning them allowing you to follow up with a barrage of strikes from your weapon of choice. The accessibility of progression in this title is irresistible the rewards that are given for complete side missions and main are more than fair, allowing you to upgrade and progress though a bewitching skill system. You also have your son as a side companion assisting you in battle as well as being a key character in the story having a major effect on the narrative. Your son Atreus can be used to attack enemies from a distance and be used to advance to new room and progress though levels and assists is tricky but fun puzzles. The graphics are unbelievably beautiful, unseen  I’m a game of this type. The miraculous terrain you travel is extremely realistic and vibrant, the surroundings are just down right prepossessing and gorgeous. The Nordic style of the environment is perfect for both combat and appealing to the eye. The water simulation in this game is a almost perfect example on how games have evolved from 2D side scroller to game that are unrecognisable from real life.  The attention to detail is unmatched, it’s clear nothing from graphics, gameplay to the story weren’t rushed. The musical score is also an absolute must when is come to setting the mood. The cinematography is on points making the game one continuous shot not cutting from one scene to the next, it creates a cinematic feeling putting in the actual perspective of the character. All around this game is extremely important in the advancements of game quality, and detail. This is a game like no other, I’ve played new game+ seven time and not one have I ever got bored of it. 10/10 AMAZING!!!"
            android:textSize="20dp"
            android:lines="5" />

    </LinearLayout>

    </LinearLayout>


</RelativeLayout>
